# Piyaporn Lahr

15 Pembroke House, Hallfield Estate, London W2 6HG

Mobile: 07543516910 | Email: piyapornlahr@gmail.com | LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/piyapornlahr

#### **PERSONAL DETAILS**

Nationality: Thai with Definite Right to remain and work in the UK

Languages: English, Thai (native)

#### **PERSONAL PROFILE**

Having worked in health care for ten years, I am reliable, experienced in working with others to achieve a certain objective on time and with excellence. I am a fast learner with a desire to learn. With my passion in IT, I decided to give myself the opportunity to step into it by attending AWS Re/start programme and now I undertake a 12-week intensive coding, programming and software development training at \_nology.

#### **QUALIFICATIONS**

AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner (Credential ID: 0ENDS99BFER1QWC9), WAES, London, May 2022

BSc Nursing Science (1st), Naresuan University, Thailand, 2012

#### **EXPERIENCES**

### Team Leader, CAREUK (2019-2023)

- Help manage a department, lead and supervise a team of carers to ensure high-quality care and support to residents in the nursing home.
- Regularly liaise with families, healthcare professionals and other stakeholders to ensure the well-being
  of residents.

### **Registered Nurse, Bangkok Phitsanulok Hospital** (2018-2019)

- Carried out assessments of patients and created care plans
- Provided care along with monitoring and administering medication
- Helped onboard new members of staff in the team

## Registered nurse, Buddhachinaraj Phitsanulok Hospital (2012-2018)

- As part of the Medicine department delivered care to patients pre and post operation
- Collected and analysed infection data for the ward on a monthly basis using Microsoft excel
- Helped train more junior members of staff and nursing students on how to deliver the most effective care

# **KEY SKILLS & INTERESTS**

- HTML
- CSS/ SCSS
- JavaScript
- AWS services
- Python (fundamental)
- SQL (fundamental)
- Linux OS (fundamental)
- Microsoft (Word, Excel, PowerPoint)
- Can speak Thai fluently (Native)